<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Wawa_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Wawa Fleet Data Request</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Wawa Fleet Card Program Fleet Data Needed</subject>
    <textOnly>{!Contact.Salutation} {!Contact.LastName},

Congratulations, your Wawa fleet account has been approved.

Before your account can be setup, I will need your driver and vehicle information. Please fill out and email the attached Fleet Information Form back to me as soon as possible. The vehicle description you provide will appear on the second line of your cards, under your company name, as well as appearing on your reports. Driver names will also appear on your reports.

A card will be assigned to each vehicle you list. You can provide Driver ID numbers on the form, or you can let our computer assign them.  Each Driver’s ID will work with any of your vehicle cards.

If you have any questions about the Fleet Information Form, please feel free to contact me at {!User.Phone}.

Again, congratulations on your new Wawa fleet account. I look forward to helping you run your business more efficiently.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
Phone - {!User.Phone}
{!User.Email}





This communication may contain confidential, proprietary or legally privileged information. It is intended only for the person(s) to whom it is addressed. If you are not an intended recipient, you may not use, read, retransmit, disseminate or take any action in reliance upon it. Please notify the sender that you have received it in error and immediately delete the entire communication, including any attachments. This communication is not intended to create or modify any obligation, contract or warranty of Wawa, Inc., unless Wawa, Inc. clearly expresses such an intent.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
