<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <attachedDocuments>Inside_Sales/SuperAmerica_App_Waived_fees.docx</attachedDocuments>
    <attachedDocuments>Inside_Sales/SuperAmerica_Sell_Sheets.pdf</attachedDocuments>
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Respond to a request for additional information. Attach application form</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>SuperAmerica</letterhead>
    <name>SA Fleet - App with Info</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Here is the SA Fleet Card Program information you requested</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

Thank you for your interest in the SA Fleet Card Program.

Below you will find some additional information about our SA Fleet Card Program to help you consider our widely accepted SA Fleet Card as the one-card solution for all your fueling needs.


We save you money. Robust fuel rebates at all SuperAmerica locations.
We save you time. You’ll enjoy the convenience of a single fueling card program and one, easy-to-read invoice. You can also easily download transaction data from the web right to QuickBooks or Excel each month.
We give you control. Detailed reports show how and where you spent your fueling money, so you can account for every penny.
We make it convenient. Your drivers only need to carry one card to fuel and save at any participating location.





You can find a complete list of accepting locations at http://superamerica.com/locations/

It’s easy to enroll. Simply complete the attached application form and fax it back to me at {!User.Fax}. You can also scan and email the form back to me at the email address below.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
Phone - {!User.Phone}
Fax - {!User.Fax}
Email - {!User.Email}



CONFIDENTIALITY NOTICE: &quot;This message contains confidential information of WEX Inc. It is intended only for the use of the designated recipient(s) stated above and further distribution of the information is prohibited. If you have received this message in error, please notify sender immediately by telephone or reply by e-mail and delete the entire message and any attachments.&quot;

WEX Inc., 97 Darling Avenue, South Portland, ME 04106


This is an advertisement from WEX Inc. If you no longer wish to receive future email advertisements from {!User.Email}, email us to unsubscribe. Please be sure to include your name, company name and email address in the email.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
