<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Send after FD is Collected</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>ExxonMobil_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>FD Complete - Next Steps</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>ExxonMobil Fleet Card</subject>
    <textOnly>{!Contact.FirstName}, 

Thank you for taking the time to go through the card set up process.  I have attached the Fleet Data form I completed while on the phone with you.   Please keep this for your records.

You should receive two packages in the mail in the next 7 - 10 business days.  The first will contain the cards (mailed from our Partners in South Portland, ME). Included will be instructions on accessing your account online (www.exxonmobilfleetonline.com / https://www.exxonmobiluniversalonline.com/online/).  The Second (mailed from Denver, CO) will contain your Driver ID Numbers (DIDs).  These two packages may not arrive together or even in the same week.  

Without the DIDs the cards cannot be used though they are active once they are set up.  You will be able to make transactions as soon you have them if you know your DIDs in advance (you provided the numbers during set up).  You should be able to get DIDs from the website as well, once you have the cards.   

Feel free to call if something should arise before then.  As a sales representative, my ability to help at this stage is limited but I will do what I can to provided assistance.  Alternatively, you can reach our customer service by calling 800-492-0669.  


Brian Fitzpatrick
Fuel Services Specialist
ExxonMobil Fuel Services
Phone: (847) 440-1724
Fax:     (207) 791-1610
Email:  bfitzpatrick@fleetlink.com
www.exxonmobilfleetoffers.com/brianfitzpatrick

CONFIDENTIALITY NOTICE: This message contains confidential information of Wright Express Corporation. It is intended only for the use of the designated recipient(s) stated above and further distribution of the information is prohibited. If you have received this message in error, please notify the sender immediately by telephone or reply e-mail and delete the entire message and any attachments</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
