<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Preshow email for contacts and attendees</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>WEX_Travel1</letterhead>
    <name>2013 Eye4Travel Preshow email</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Stop by the WEX Bank booth (#11) for a chance to win an iPad</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

Attending Eye4Travel in Chicago? Stop by the WEX Bank booth (#11) and enter to win an iPad. While you are there, we’d love to chat with you about how WEX Travel can make a significant impact on your business. With WEX Travel you can pay the right amount, at the right time, to the right supplier through your existing systems all while generating additional revenue for your business.

Additional benefits include:

99.9% reconciliation
Automate processes
Optimize cash flow
International and Domestic payments
Control Spend


For over a decade, WEX  has been leading the way in single-use payment technology to the travel industry. Several of the largest online travel agencies payments are powered by WEX Travel. To learn more, visit our Resource Center: http://www.wexinc.com/virtual-payments/insights/videos/

&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = &quot;urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office&quot; /&gt;

Please stop by and introduce yourself.  In the meantime, please do not hesitate to contact me with questions.


Sincerely,
{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
Phone - {!User.Phone}
Cell - {!User.MobilePhone}
{!User.Email}



CONFIDENTIALITY NOTICE: This message contains confidential information WEX Inc.. It is intended only for the use of the designated recipient(s) stated above and further distribution of the information is prohibited. If you have received this message in error, please notify sender immediately by telephone or reply by e-mail and delete the entire message and any attachments.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
